

Mathematician & Aspiring Data Scientist

I graduated from Marian University of Indiana with a degree in Mathematics with a minor in Physics. I have both tutored and taught mathematics as well as worked in police dispatch before deciding to make a career change into the field of data science and analysis. In order to accomplish this, I worked through a data science and machine learning bootcamp with Coding Dojo.

EXPERIENCE

2019

La Plaza, Indianapolis, IN

Math & Science Teacher

- Created lesson plans for 8-12 year olds.
- Generated interest in science through project focused lesson planning.

2022-2023

MUPD, Indianapolis, IN

Dispatcher

- Worked with university security software.
- Took emergency calls and quickly directed first responders.

2018

Indy Reads, Indianapolis, IN

Volunteer

- Organized books for store shelves.
- Helped setup for community outreach programs.

PORTFOLIO

github.com/JamisonHunter/Product-Sales-Prediction

Prediction of Product Sales (In Progress)

Python, Tensorflow, Sklearn

github.com/JamisonHunter/Adult-Income-Prediction

Income Prediction For Guidance Counseling (In Progress)

Python, Tensorflow, Sklearn

https://github.com/JamisonHunter/IMDB-Data-Analysis

IMDB Data Analysis 2000-2007 (In Progress)

Python, TMDB API

https://github.com/JamisonHunter/Chicago-Crime-Data-Analysis

Chicago Crime Data Analysis 2017-2022 (In Progress)

Python, Tableau

SKILLS

- Python
- Data Analysis
- HTML & CSS
- Teaching
- Russian

EDUCATION

2018-2022

B.A. Mathematics

Marian University

2023

Data Science & Machine Learning

Coding Dojo

INTERESTS

- Language
- Programming
- Physics
- Rocketry